Hisarcik.
Gevye.
Yeni Kale (The New Castle)
Tus Bazaar.
And Akkhisar.
Baysungur and the brave
men that followed him.
To make those lands become Turk lands...
...they fought hard.
And they became martyrs in the end.
God willing, we will become
martyrs after them, my Bey.
One of us may become
a martyr but with the help
of Allah, a thousand
more will go for shahada.
With the help of Allah.
Orhan.
My Bey.
Inform llbay.
Whoever martyred Baysungur
and the brave men with him...
...he should sneak into Lucas’ ranks...
..and learn about it.
As you command my Bey.
We are going to...
...strike that infidel so hard.
Strike him so hard!
My Bey, I think...
...we should go for Gevye.
It has a weak defence.
I think we should go for Hisarcik castle.
That's on of the most
prosperous castles of Byzantine.
There will be good booty.
No.
All those castles are our targets.
But the most important one is..
..due to its location..
...the Akhisar.
If we take Akhisar...
...then the land trade around
it will be under our control.
This will also harm Karesi Bey too.
Tell me, are the armies ready?
Our army is read to
defeat the infidels, my Bey.
Alright.
Bayhan Bey and Gencer Bey.
When the bring their
armies in front of Akhisar...
...then..
...we will go for a great conquest.
Since you mentioned Karesi Bey.
I got word from Karadin my Bey.
Karasi Bey increased the taxes
and caused unrest among people.
You should focus on Sogut, Begun Hatun.
Not Karadin.
The trade shouldn't be interrupted.
Bala Hatun is right.
Begum Hatun..
...take your duty in Sogut.
As you command my Bey.
Yusuf Bey, Saruca Bey.
You are responsible for Sogut's
security and caravans' safety.
As you command my Bey.
Orhan Alaeddin.
Get ready.
Before we conquer Akhisar, we will...
...raid the villages and
bases that Supply...
...Akhfear with ammunition and food.
As you command my Bey.
We will..
...take Baysungur's revenge.
Baysungur, whom you killed...
...was one of Osman’s closest men.
He is in hell together with others.
We will see..
...what Osman will do without his spies.
Osman is just like...
...a cornered cockroach right now.
He'll attack.
I'm not afraid of him.
Osman’s daughter...
If I took Fatma Hatun from him...
...that will devastate him.
Osman would come after us.
And to lure him to my trap..
...I'll plan step by step slowly.
My Bey.
These days...
..I feel worried.
So do you, Bala.
I'm fine my Bey.
Same old, same old.
Well...
Just like how I attend the battle...
...your duty here is as difficult as mine.
I know why you're worried.
I know.
Gonca and Holofira, right?
You don't miss a thing.
Tell me. We have all this trouble.
How could you tell?
From your eyes.
But know this.
They must make peace now.
Enemies attack from all sides.
We must have peace in the family.
We'll be united.
Don't worry my Bey.
I'll find a way to make peace.
They're young.
Of course.
It's because they're young.
But...
But after they learn from you..
...they’ll be proper Bey Hatuns.
God willing.
Our children and the tribe
are yours to protect Bala.
May Allah protect you.
Girbay, you’ll find the
dastards who killed Baysungur.
Even if they hide under rocks..
...you'll find them
no matter where they hide.
This is your only duty.
Don't worry my Shehzade.
Alps found where Baysungur was martyred.
I'll go there and follow the trail.
But whoever it is..
he must've found all the spies we have.
Baysungur said it's not Karesibey...
..nor was it Lukas, but...
But...
But it must be someone close to Lukas.
Whoever it is, knows Lukas.
Keep your eyes and ears open.
Go soon. Come on.
As you wish my Shehzade.
Attention! Osman Beyl
Beys
Alps
Those who know Shahada..
...will never be defeated.
Now tell me.
Are you with me the path to Shahada?
We're with you my Bey!
Will you help me make
the infidels take the knee?
We will my bey!
Do you swear to..
...fight until your last breath
-We do my bey!
Then I promise to be the
one leading in the front.
May Allah help us.
Amen.
May our war be holy.
Ameen.
May you have an easy journey my bey
Allah who makes the clouds move...
...and the enemy armies fail..
...for the sake of our
martyrs who died while
saying the shahada,
don't turn away our prayers.
Amen.
Give strength to my bey and his alps.
Ameen
Defeate the enemies and grant us
the vocitory, God willing.
Ameen.
Get ready, we are going to Sogut Bazaar.
We will make Sogut the biggest
and busiest bazaar around here.
Come on
My bey, thes men are mong the
most respected en in Karadin Castle.
They want to tell you something.
Tell me what your problem is.
My bey, the taxes you decided for
us has put too much pressure on us.
We don't make much.
We can't shoulder this sum.
Osman Bey didn't do this,
he showed us mercy.
We’ve started to miss
the old days, Karesi Bey.
We pay the sum Osman Bey decided on.
We can’t afford any more than that.
If not you won't be able to stop
an upcoming riot Karesi Bey.
You money hungry dogs.
You ungrateful folk.
How dare you act
disrespectly in my presence?
Osman isn't here anymore.
The old order is no more.
It's my rule.
The price of living a peaceful
life behind these walls...
...will be paid.
The destiny of those
who won't is horrible.
Now get out of my sight.
Get lost.
Sancar.
Yes, my bey.
I don’t want to witness
disrespect like this ever again.
The one who raises
their voice will be silenced.
As you wish my bey.
Tell me.
Is then any word from Kanyumaz?
He is following Osman Bey's every move.
But there is still no
word from him, my bey.
Osman acted keen
with the trade issue but...
..because of his spies’ deaths...
...he will attack like a wounded animal.
Continue to watch him.
We won't let Osman have a chance.
Never.
Bala Hatun is coming to the Bazaar today.
Make sure we are ready.
I don't want anything to be unfinished.
Hello.
They told me this bazaar
is under your responsibility.
Begum Hatun, right?
Yes, it is.
My name is Veronica.
I'm a trader.
I bring caravans to the
bazaar from China to Rome.
I've seen your face for the first time.
And I haven't heard your name before.
Because that's my
first visit to the borders.
I wanted to have a look at Sogut Bazaar,
after Thea rd it and I'm glad that I did.
What I heard was not even close.
So, you are trading with the
personal permission of .the Emperor?
Yes.
And I want to trade with you very much.
Let’s know you first.
Trader Veronica..
Please, explore our bazaar.
Thank you
From China to Rome, huh?
Investigate this woman well.
Let's see if she is a trader
as great as she claims.
Allah is the Greatest!
Baysungur.
My warrior, then, you did a great job
What am I going td do?
I'm going to die of starvation!
I'm going to suffer and die! I'll die!
What am I going to do, my brothers?
Where should we put
the Cerkutay Bey's goat?
My brother!
Welcome, Bala Hatun
Thank you. Thank you. May it be easy.
Ulgen.
Welcome, Bala Hatun.
Thank you. Thank you.
Tell me, Ulgen. How do the
people treat Holofira Hatun?
Like fire.
Everyone sulks when
they hear Holofira's name.
So, the rebellion have made
the situation worse, huh?
We need to extinguish that
fire before it gets bigger, Ulgen.
They don't know Holofira.
If they do, that fire
will go off by itself.
They will know her.
May it be easy, sisters.
-Welcome, Gonca Hatun
-Welcome!
Hatun.
Welcome, Gonca Hatun.
Welcome.
May it be easy, Hatuns.
We say may it be easy,
sisters! What's going on?
You don't want it to be easy, huh?
I'm talking to you!
Thank you, Holofira Hatun.
-Thank you.
-Welcome.
Welcome, Bala Hatun.
-Welcome, Bala Hatun.
Tomorrow we are going to feed
all our merchants in the bazaar.
We will enlarge our bazaar
with prosperity, God willing.
God willing.
Fatma will take care of the food.
Bala.
I am back, Bala.
I came to settle our records.
Hazal Hatun.
You are responsible for the
classification of the upcoming goods.
As you command Bala Hatun.
The most important duty...
...belongs to you, my daughters.
The stalls.
From now on, Holofira
will be responsible for the...
...stalls in North.
And the South..
....will be under Gonca's responsibility.
As you command mother.
I know it's not my place to say...
..but does Holofira Hatun..
...know the traditions in our bazaar?
What if she can't make
it in time for tomorrow?
My daughters will support each other.
Holofira is the
daughter-in-law of Kayi family.
Let it be known!
Also, my daughter will
learn everything on duty.
I will not disappoint you mother Bala.
Gonca will help you
with anything you lack.
Right Gonca?
I will do what's necessary, mother.
Good.
Kayi's hatuns go on,
show me your skills.
Until tomorrow, I want all
the food and stalls be ready.
As you command Bala Hatun.
My girls.
I trust you.
Don't disappoint me.
Come on.
Come on Gulce.
Fatma Hatun.
This will suit you.
Get down!
My Bey, alps are sneaking in quietly.
Boran, tell me.
How did they settle in this mine?
Resources go to
Akhisar castle and the
base that protects
the castle from outside.
They loaded them onto the
carts, they will go out soon.
We will destroy the mine first.
Then we will go after the caravan.
We will..
..enter the base with their swords!
Water!
Oh Allah!
Allah is Everlasting!
Allah is Truthful!
Even if we killed a thousand
of you, we'd still feel anger.
Allah is the Greatest!
These cruel dastards are going to hell!
Martyrs will never die!
Please. Please don’t kill us.
Pull out your hand
Please! Please!
Come here! Come here!
Don't worry.
We would never harm an innocent man.
Boran. Water!
Okay my Bey.
May God bless you.
Allah bless you.
Water! Water!
Travel in peace.
Boran.
My Bey.
Give me the pouch.
Here my Bey.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Come on.
Travel in peace.
Get up.
AIps help.
Thank you.
May God bless you.
If the poor can't eat...
..I can't eat a single bite.
So this is yours.
Travel in peace.
Allah bless you.
Come on. Let's go after
them before they get away.
Let's go.
Byzantine Town
This defense...
...is as good as that of a castle's.
They’re growing the Akhisar storage.
They're watching.
When they see a sign of invasion....
...they will immediately
signal other castes using torches.
Those torches will never be fired.
Brother.
Is everything ready?
Yes brother.
Waiting to be ordered.
Only thing the support army will see....
...is the smoke from the ashes.
Yes.
You'll protect the torches Alaeddin.
When you're in position, we'll attack!
This den of devils
will collapse in itself.
Alright.
May our war be blessed.
Come on.
Bala Hatun.
Enjoy it while you can.
I swore to take everything from you.
Soon.
Mother.
I added 10 more cauldrons for tomorrow.
We never prepared this much before.
As days go by, we grow in number.
You did well.
We'll need more.
Tomorrow, everyone will see
how we grew our market, God willing.
Hug your daughter.
Hug her, Bala.
Hug her while you can.
Bala Hatun.
Begum Hatun.
What do you think of our bazaar?
I wish to get your advice
because of your talents with trade.
Good job Begum Hatun.
You can't say for certain at day one.
I wish to build a bazaar
worthy of Osman Bey and you.
If you see any mistakes, tell me.
It seems like this duty has
helped you a lot, Begum Hatun.
Of course.
May those who saw me fit
for this duty live a long life.
Come drink some sherbet.
I don't have time.
I'll go to inspect the
Yenisehir tradesmen.
Next time, God willing.
So you decided to shave
off your thorns, Begum...
Let's see what you're after now...
Fatma.
Mother.
Keep watch over this place, daughter.
Come on Kismet, we are leaving.
Sister.
I've prepared the alps for the
safety of the caravan tomorrow.
But working with Saruca...
I don't like it at all, just so you know.
We will do whatever
Osman Bey tells us to do.
No matter if you like it or not.
We won't be in bad terms with him.
You...
That's why you get along with Bala Hatun.
For me, then.
Until we get what we want...
..I have to hide my grudge.
But when the time comes..
...will not hold myself back
from showing my thorns Yusuf.
Just so you know.
Okay.
What’s this? Go and check.
Get him out of the way.
Alps.
That’s Osman Bey. Attack.
Yes, Osman Bey.
I came to take my men's revenge.
For my brother.
Gather.
The real issue is the headquarters.
When it falls..
...the castle will be unprotected.
Boran, load the gunpowder into the carts.
We're leaving quickly.
As you wish my bey.
Where do you come from?
Do you have permission to trade?
Search it.
I come from the Greek lands at the Borders,
I don't have permission to trade but...
Those who don't have permission
have no place here, move your cart.
We don't have permission.
But we have many precious goods.
If you let us pass, everyone wins.
What do you mean?
Most of the load of the trade from
Iranian territory is on our shoulder.
It means each of these
caravans carries booty.
Whoever clears our road and helps us...
...takes his share.
They have the trade
permission. Let them pass
We'll see each other again.
Let's go.
Alps, when Alaaddin's Alps
take their place, we'll attack.
There are kids and women
inside. Everyone shall be cautious.
As you command, my Bey.
We'll see huh?
Let's go.
How did you know they
were going to let us pass?
Beys, nobles and captives
are sold in this bazaar.
Do you think some
jackals cannot be sold here?
We'll support each
other in this bazaar and...
...we'll destroy this den of dogs.
We'll do it!
Come on, sisters! Make
sure all the stalls are tidy.
No job will be left for
tomorrow, God willing.
Allah is great! God willing,
the Hatuns will finish on time.
Hatuns, be hasty.
The stalls must be ready until tomorrow.
Check the goods, too.
There must be no mistake, okay?
I heard the honesty in the
Turkish Bazaars all the time.
I've seen it was true.
I'm sorry. I haven't introduce myself.
Trade Veronica.
As far as I know,
you are the brides of Osman Bey, aren't you?
We are.
Welcome. I'm Gonca.
Holofira.
-Is it your first time in Sogut?
-It is.
But loved Sogut.
I mean I feel like...
..I knew this place before.
And I am Hazal Hatun.
I am Ayhan Bey's Hatun.
Where are you coming from?
From China.
Gonca Hatun.
Holofira Hatun. I have
some business to handle but...
...I want to know you more
familiarly as soon as possible.
-Of course.
I heard something but...
Holofira Hatun wanted to
put Greek Hatuns on the stalls.
She didn't like you.
But Gonca Hatun didn't accept it.
As if it wasn’t enough
she caused the death
of many of our sons,
she doesn't like us, too?
Does she want what we earn?
Let's go, Hatuns.
Gonca Hatun.
We want to work on your stalls from now on.
How can it be, sisters?
Everyone has her duty.
And don't you hear my mother?
It can't happen.
Come on. Come on, sisters.
Go back to your duties.
Then, we won't open our stalls.
Let’s go back to the tribe, Hatunsi
No one is going anywhere.
This stall needs to be ready for tomorrow.
We gave a promise to Bala Hatun.
-Holofira Hatun.
-No!
Until the stall is ready...
..no one is leaving.
Hatuns!
Can I come in my Bey?
Come in.
My Bey...
the people of Karadin quiets down.
But they are holding a grudge.
If it leads to a riot...
What diminishes the state is...
..the self serving commanders, Sancar.
I won't let it happen.
What do we do my Bey?
What is your command?
Whoever is confusing the people
and tries to fool the people..
...will be silenced right away.
I am the state here.
Whoever objects me, will be killed.
May I come in my Bey?
Come in.
My Bey.
Osman Bey attacked.
To whom?
Where?
In the Kartal Yeni region, my Bey.
He's attacking the mines and bases.
Kartal Yeni?
Osman Bey... What is
he after this time, my bey?
Dark Osman..
He wants to take the ruler of
trade routes, the most loved...
...by the tradesmen, the Akhisar Castle.
Akhisar?
Oh no, my bey.
If Osman takes that place...
...then the tradesmen in
Karesi grounds will retreat.
We won’t get any gold, my bey.
They won't.
We will get gold.
I won't let anyone
lessen the gold I earn!
Get ready.
We are going to go to Lucas.
As you wish my bey.
Where are the others?
On the way.
Let's unload together. Come on!
In the name of Allah.
This is for Baysungur.
It's a trap! Run away!
Come on brave ones!
Don't let them breathe!
Attack!
Brother, I kill them.
I kill them.
But it's not going away.
The fire in my heart is not going out.
How will my sadness end?
My pain is still there too, Cerkutay.
I keep remembering Baystingur's eyes.
His sacrifices.
How is this going to end, Cerkutay?
How?
You are feeling sad for Baysungur.
Don't.
It's time for revenge, not grieving!
Pull yourselves together!
Today is not the day for lamenting
Today is the day we rise up!
Lucas.
Those walls you hide behind!
They won't be
able to protect you!
They won't!
Come on brave ones!
Alps.
Get ready.
It's time.
Let's kill those dogs.
Come on.
Allah is the Greatest!
We are under attack!
They broke in!
Light the torches!
The Righteous!
Allah is the Greatest!
I have arrived brother!
Gonca.
Don't be afraid.
No one will be hurt here.
From now on, we'll protect you..
...and everything you own.
God protect you.
Thank you.
May Allah protect us all.
Come here.
In the name of Allah.
Praise be.
Oguz.
My Bey.
Give him water.
Turan, take him.
Give him water and clean him up.
Come here. Come.
Are you okay?
I'm okay, thanks.
Good. Go to your homes.
Is everyone okay?
Yes Shehzade. All the soldiers are okay.
Thank Allah.
The goods in the carriages are ours.
Give them to the people.
As you wish my Shehzade.
Thank you.
Thank you Ekrem Bey.
You came to us...
...all the way from Ahiska lands.
You supported us.
And attacked the enemy with us.
Thank you.
Ahizka Turks will follow Osman Bey in
his path and support him my Shehzade.
Thank you.
The goods from Akhisar storage....
It won't last them long.
We'll get them eventually.
Those who kill Turks.
...will end up dead at
the end of our sword.
I swear to Allah, we'll avenge
our martyrs and Baysungur.
They'll either surrender...
...or drown in blood.
Allah is the Greatest!
Commander Lucas.
What is it, Hristo?
The base near Akhisar castle was invaded.
Who raided it?
Osman.
He attacked the Greek fire.
The base fell.
They invaded suddenly.
We couldn't see.
They were too many Commander Lukas.
You clumsy men!
What did you do as Osman attacked?
Did you run and hide?
You're a shame to Byzantine!
Why didn't you die?
How dare you face me?
The mine carriages full of iron...
...they were fir...
-Shut up!
No excuses!
You said you didn't see?
Yes.
Take them.
I'll punish them later.
What is your order sir?
Osman's avenging his spies.
He wants Akhisar castle next.
But he'll face us when he gets there.
Give the order Hristo!
Gather the army
As you wish sir.
And you...
...will go to Osman as a messenger.
You..
will tell him not to enter a war he can't win.
Come here Osman!
Finally, it's the day
our swords will clash!
Come here.
Come here. Leave it here.
It's lovely.
Sort them by color.
Okay Hatuns?
Let's hurry a bit, we're
running out of time.
Gonca.
This is your doing.
You made them hate me.
Holofira, enough.
I'm telling you, I didn't do anything.
Besides, not everyone has to like you.
It works in your favor right?
Tell me.
Who knows what you're thinking about.
Besides, what will happen if they...
...like you more Gonca?
What are you trying to say?
How would that help me Holofira?
It's clear.
You've memorized the
tricks of your mother very well.
If you...
...ever say anything about this.
..I'll make you regret it.
Bless your hands, sisters!
Vegetables on this side.
The carpets go there, we will
lay them down under the tables.
Fatma Hatun.
Do you need help?
Thank you Saruca Bey.
The alps and sisters can do it.
Fatma Hatun.
Congrats for your new duty.
Then again we are used to
seeing you shooting arrows but...
...this job suits you as well.
When did you saw
me with a bow and an arrow?
Oh, that time you couldn't
shoot the target!
Of course.
You must remember that time well.
Turks are so generous.
You can hardly see this
kind of preparation at bazaars.
Thank you.
Is this your first time
at a Turkish bazaar?
We are always like this.
Merchant Veronica.
I see that you've met Fatma Hatun.
Yes.
She a very good archer.
Praise be! Praise be! Praise be!
May Allah protect her from the evil eye.
Both her heart and her face are pretty.
Just like Bala.
I'm very pleased to meet you Fatma Hatun.
Begum Hatun, excuse me.
I still have a lot more
to see at the bazaar.
Evil eyes... Go.
Excuse me.
Beys.
The goods we will receive
tomorrow are very important.
The women are trying
to prepare the stalls.
Everything's with you right?
Yes sister.
Osman Bey.
We've been ready ever
since he told us to be ready.
But I don't know how things
are with Yusuf Bey, of course.
Allah..
-The horsemen will set out immediately.
They'll support the defence of the castle.
And the infantry...
...will pass the the tunnel of Kuzgun...
...and infiltrate into the castle.
No one will hear anything.
I want no mistake.
As you command, Commander Lukas.
Get out.
You can't stop Osman alone, Lukas.
You've increased the hatred of Osman.
Now, you can't beat him alone.
Then, I'll bury him with his own hatred!
I'll stand before him even
if I know I'm going to die.
Do it. Do it.
Of course.
But I will come with you.
What are you talking about, Karasi Bey?
Look.
If Osman takes Aksihar Castle, he
will take the control of the trade road.
My trade on the land will disappear.
You think I'll risk this, Lukas?
You always act for your own
benefit, Karasi Bey. Always!
What do you propose
We'll share everything in half.
We will stop Osman together but...
...you will give my share from
the trade on Aksihar Castle.
How are you going to stop Osman?
Tell me if you are up for the deal first.
Okay. Let it be as you want.
Let's stay as two armies
in one front, Karasi Bey.
Good.
Wait for news from me.
I followed you once, Karasi.
I won’t do the same
mistake for the second time.
I'll be prepared.
Stableman! Take care of this!
This horse is new.
Whose is it?
Be sure it is well-fed.
This horse is a...
...gift from Commander
Lukas to our new guest.
Isn't this gifted horse for the
women, who killed Osman Bey's spy?
Not one. I heard she
killed so many spies that
she destroyed all the
intelligence Kayi had.
What is the name of
this guest? If I know her name...
...when I need
to prepare the horse...
You will be commanded then.
Just do you job.
Really, what is her name?
I don’t know. I heard she
only speaks to Commander Lukas.
Sancar...
Karasi Bey...
So, you are doing
something with Lukas again.
NEAR AKSIHAR, KAYI HEADQUARTERS
Peace be with you.
Peace be upon you.
Welcome Beys.
Finally, your troops joined our army.
Thank you.
We are by your side with
all our forces, Osman Bey.
Before the Kayi flag is
placed on the walls of Akhisar...
...and the call of
Mohammad echoes there...
...we are not Beys, we are just
soldiers under your command my Bey.
Thank you.
The villages that send
rations to Akhisar...
...and bases that send
weapons and ammunition there...
...have been destroyed, with the
permission of Allah, Thank Allah.
Thank Allah.
The blood we spilled
in infidel villages today...
...will be the assurance of what
we are going to do in those castles.
My Bey, that dog Lucas
heard about our attack.
He must have started gathering his army.
Will Lucas enter the castle to defend it?
Or is he going to try to
break our siege from butside?
He can bring all his army in the castle.
He can stand against
us with all his power.
Lucas has nothing he can take...
...other than surrendering,
defeat and death!
Now, at dawn..
...our army will go for Akhisar.
And take position in
front of the castle for siege.
To take Baysungur's revenge.
To take our martyrs revenge.
We will rain wrath down on them!
With the help of Allah.
Oghuz, isn't that Lucas' man?
Yes.
Make way.
What are you doing here?
You killed my brother Baysungur!
How dare you come here?
Brother, wait.
I am here as Commander Lucas' messenger.
I came to see Osman Bey.
Alps, take his weapons.
My Bey.
Lucas' messenger has arrived.
He wants to talk to you.
Let him come.
Orhan.
Speak.
What does the snake tongued Lucas want?
If a war begins, it will be your end.
Your army can never breach Akhisar walls.
Byzantine soldiers will
not abstain from a war.
Commander Lucas is
giving you a chance to live.
Turn back and return to your tribes.
Is that so?
So be it.
We drew our sword already.
Before we avenge our martyrs...
....and shed blood, we'll never back down.
Go tell your master...
...that the walls of the castle will fall.
Akhisar...
...will be Kayi's.
Osman Bey, don't waste your Alps.
Shut up! Take him!
Come.
Take him.
If I were you...
..I'd kill him.
They shouldn't breathe.
If they died, everyone would forget.
They will live like this..
...so that other soldiers will learn.
Did you go to Sogut?
I didn’t.
I'm closer to them than ever.
I have them in control.
I can’t wait until tomorrow
Sofia. I'll leave soon.
I can’t let these idiots protect Akhisar.
You're right.
But I don't think it's necessary.
Osman will fall on his
knees and beg you...
...for his daughter Fatma.
You underestimate Osman.
He always has a second plan.
Don't overestimate him.
That shepherd..
...will beg us like a fool.
Tomorrow we will be victorious Lukas.
I'll bury them all in one grave.
We'll bury them together Lukas.
Who are you woman?
Kayi Tribe
So...
..Gonca....Holofira.
How was your day?
Tell me about the market.
It was good mother. My stall is ready.
But...
The Sisters gave Holofira a hard time.
They’ll get used to it.
Don't worry Mother Bala.
I'll do everything to earn their trust.
Everything will be
ready until the morning.
Praise be to my girl.
You...
..don't want war but...
...Holofira Hatun has
already started that war.
You can do anything, Holofira Hatun.
The folk are like a fist, Holofira Hatun.
They won't let anyone in easily.
It's hard to earn their trust.
Good.
I like tough things, Begum,Hatun.
That's it.
You have to stand-up strong to
not allow people to trample you.
They will respect you first...
...and then like you.
May I come in Bala Hatun?
Come in Kismet.
Bala Hatun.
There is word from Osman Bey.
Osman Bey has taken the
town and the headquarters.
They are moving towards the Castle.
Thank Allah.
Praise be!
Kismet, tell Ulgen to bring us sherbet.
Mother.
I'm not complaining about my food duty.
I really like working for the folk.
But, when will I go to war?
Will I always remain under your wings?
Come here.
What's wrong with our wings?
Besides, don't you know it?
Even if your nail gets broken..
...both your father and I get so worried.
Mother.
I can protect myself.
I train the the sisters!
I even defeated Yusuf Bey
and Saruca Bey in archery.
No.
I can't stand that.
If I go, then you can come with me.
But I won't send you
off to the fight alone.
Mother...
You'll understand once
you're a mother too.
Ever since Baysungur passed away...
...there has been this
ache in my chest, brothers.
My heart burns, Cerkutay.
So does mine, brother.
While...
...he was going though...
...all that torture for the nation...
...we thought he fell as a martyr.
Then we learned that...
...he was alive and said thank Allah.
He was with us.
But just then..
We buried him ourselves..
I'll carry Baysungur's knife from now on.
Even if I kill thousand infidels..
..my pain won't die down.
Our bey said revenge first...
...and then mourning.
But neither the things we did today...
...nor the castle we will
get tomorrow helps my pain.
Beys.
Alps, what are you talking about?
Aykurt.
About our brother
Baysungur's passing, my bey.
Our brother...
We can’t stand that our martyr
passed away like that, my bey.
Hold on.
The wounds that were opened in Baysungur's
body in the most merciless way...
Is this how you are
revenging those wounds?
It's not the time to
take your heads down...
...but it's time tear the enemy
into one-thousand pieces!
Of course, our heart is on fire.
Of course, we are in pain.
But don't forget that we
will never fall into despair!
Neither we will forged,
the martyrdom of Baysungur...
...nor we will
let the enemy forget it!
My Bey tells the truth, brothers!
We won't fall into despair
so that the infidels...
...will never think
that they could pay the
martyrdom of Baysungur
and many more with a castle!
And our love for
war haven't ran out...
...and our motivation didn't die out!
Brothers!
Allah! Allah!
Heads up!
Resist!
For the ones who fell
as martyrs for the state
The days that we take our
revenge from all the infidels are near!
Of course!
We've never given up since the old times!
We’ve always stood tall
Even if one of us falls..
...another of us will go to war
with the shouts of Allah! Allah!
Allah is the greatest!
For our ghazis who shout as Allah! Allah!
For our martyrs whom we
wrapped with bloodied clothes!
For our ancestors that
expect great victories from us!
Allah is the greatest!
Mother; Mother, save me! Mother!
Fatma!
Daughter! Fatma
Where are you, daughter?
I'm coming. Where are you?
Fatma!
Mother!
Daughter.
Mother, where are you? Mother!
I'm coming, daughter.
I'm coming. I'm coming.
Fatma! Fatma!
Where are you?
Oh!
Fatma!
Mother, save me! Mother!
Where are you?
Where are you, daughter? My child
Mother!
Mother, where are you? Mother!
Where are you?
Daughter
Don't do it! Stop
Mother, save me.
Don't do this!
No!
Fatma!
No! Fatma!
No!
Fatma!
Oh Allah, don't let this dream come true.
Oh Allah, protect my children.
Near Osman Bey's Headquarters
My Beys.
My fellows.
Brave soldiers who love Allah!
I know all of you wait
to attack the enemy...
...like wild fire lit on an arrow.
It is time now.
In Allah's name..
...to build a world with
the Holy Laws of Allah...
..we'll be the executioners..
...of our enemies.
We'll be executioners!
Now it’s time.
For the state...
...for our traditions..
...and for our martyrs...
We'll walk to Shahada.
You're the brave men who reach
the target as soon as I show you it.
May Allah..
May Allah bless you all.
Ameen!
May your fists...
...be as strong as Allah's
lion, Hamza Hadrath...
...may your swords
be as sharp as Zulfiqar.
May your arrows find their targets
just like Sa'd ibn Abi Waqqas.
Amen, amen, amen!
Against oppression and sin,
may we be victorious just...
..like our Prophet...
Peace Be Upon Him..
...and his army with Allah's permission.
Ameen.
May our war be blessed.
Tell me.
Food will be given out soon.
Only women work in there, no soldiers.
We're going to get Fatma from there.
At the right time...
Okay.
The cart?
It's ready, ma'am.
We hid it in the forest.
It seems Holofira got
the stalls ready on time.
She's an ambitious woman.
She thinks I'm the reason of Hatun's anger
She forgets what she caused...
and blames me.
She targets my most vulnerable point...
...which is my mother.
You are the Hatun of Shehzade.
Hide your wound, Gonca.
You have no friends
anymore. Don't forget this.
Especially, Holofira.
If she takes the support
of the family in the future...
Despite all the pain in my heart.
...I didn't attack her
where she is vulnerable.
Never.
Your mercy is making you make mistakes.
That war has begun.
If you say that you can't fight...
..not you..
...but shahzade Alaeddin will lose.
I would never let Alaeddin get harmed.
If she wants war...
then I will give it to her.
But Bala shouldn't realize it.
Thanks for your hard work, sisters.
It looks good.
Alps, take the goats to slaughterhouse.
Sisters, bring the cut meat.
Okay Fatma Hatun.
Come on.
People of Sogut are waiting for food!
Then they will have
to wait a little longer.
Who are you?
What are you doing
here? Leave immediately.
I am not going anywhere without you.
Osman’s daughter.
Are you out of your mind?
You are going to kidnap me from Sogut?
Don't worry about that.
Fatma Hatun.
Sisters!
You!
You will beg to live!
I will drown you
in your own blood!
Are you going to talk or fight?
You are a coward that
hides behind her mask!
And you will die as a coward!
Bala trained you well.
But fun is over.
Turks..
...think they can stand
against me. Pitiful.
Wrap this snake..
...in a carpet.
We are leaving.
Oh Allah, protect them.
Bala?
Thanks Ulgen.
In the name of Allah, the
merciful, the beneficent.
You've been acting weird since morning.
Are you okay?
I have an odd feeling.
I had a nightmare last night Ulgen.
What is it? Tell me.
I saw Fatma.
May Allah bless us.
Amen.
Let's think beautifully.
Yes, sure.
Did you send hatuns with her this morning?
I did of course.
She went there with Gonca and Holofira.
Good. Good.
Fatma's right.
You can't send her to battle.
I won’t.
She can only come if I go.
No other way
I'll watch over her.
Okay.
But, you know.
She'll get married.
One day...
She's old enough.
Men will want her as a wife.
So?
They might.
If we don't let her go...
...no one can take my girl, Ulgen.
So, you can control people's feelings?
Listen to me.
Is there something you won't tell me?
No. Why would I?
Is there?
No.
Okay.
Let's go then. I want to see my daughter.
-I need to relax.
-Let's go.
Akhisar Caste
Reinforce the gate!
Increase the units 4 times their size!
Today no one will enter this gate!
Archers!
You will even shoot the birds.
Osman!
You'll be crushed by an
army scarier than death.
Put it there! There!
Hurry! Now!
Here! Here! Put it there! There! Come on!
Fearless sons of the Holy Rome.
I have full faith in you.
Osman.
Osman thinks he's invincible.
Today we'll put him through hell!
Long Live Commander Lucas!
Come on Hatuns. Prepare
them all before Bala Hatun arrives.
She'll see how a real bazaar is set up.
She needs to learn.
Begum Hatun.
What is it?
You're leaving early. Where to?
Thanks to you we made good deals.
My work was done quickly today.
Good.
I'm happy to hear.
Did you meet Bala Hatun before?
No.
Not yet.
Now...
...if you excuse me...
If that's the case...
...then it's time that you meet her.
Bala Hatun is coming here.
I would've loved to but...
...I don't have time.
I made a promise to a merchant.
Next time.
It won't take long.
Come, drink some sherbet.
Bala Hatun will be here soon.
As I said I would've loved to but....
...I'm very busy today.
We'll talk tomorrow.
I'll meet Bala Hatun then too.
We'll trade a lot more, Begum Hatun
If that's the case...
Be quick.
There he is.
Karesi Bey.
We are going on a conquest.
I would say you're here to
support us, to work with us but...
...whenever we come across
you, you only make us turn back.
You're right Osman.
I'm here to make you turn back.
To tell you not to attack Akhisar.
Supporting us...
...working with us...
We can forget these.
And now you tell us not
to attack the infidels' land.
Is this how you act as a Turk?
Osman.
Is it your place to question
how much of a Turk I am?
Not for the infidels..
...I'm against you for
the future of my nation.
Sancar.
You see it.
Lucas and I have an agreement.
From now on my caravans
will travel to Bitinya...
...across Akhisar.
What I'm saying is...
...that Akhisar is a
point in my trade route.
I'll consider the attack you lash out...
...out on me, on my nation.
If you attack Akhisar...
What will you do?
Look, I won't care that you're Turkish...
...and we share the same lineage.
I'll attack you on every front.
Here is the battlefield.
Here is your opponent.
Come on Karesi Bey.
Come on, face me.
Osman.
Know that disrespect against
me never be left unpunished.
I'll finish the ones
you worked with first.
Then..
Then your time will come, too.
Whatever you say, Osman.
Let it be as you said.
When I destroy your world,
I'll make you remember your words..
Who sunk the ship? Could you find him?
Who put the stones on the chests?
Huh, Karasi Bey?
Osman.
Osman, of course.
I'll check the cart.
I'll take care of it, Yusuf.
I know what goes out
and in the bazaar well.
Don't kill these ones.
Both of them the sons of
the Beys. They will be useful.
Pull over there.
Trader.
What are you doing here?
We are returning from the bazaar.
Where are you going?
We’ll check the cart. It’s the rules.
-We need to check what you are carrying.
-Of course, please.
What do you have in the chests? Open them.
Come on.
Come on, come on.
Open them open.
Come on.
Come on, come on, quickly. Come on.
Ambush!
Who the hell are you?
Do you know on whom
you set ambush, dastards?
Don't let them talk. Finish this now!
Bring the caged cart! Come on!
Leave me! Leave me! Dastards! Leave me!
Leave me! Yusuf!
-Hold on, Yusuf!
-You think you can get away with this, huh?
Leave me!
Come on!
Come!
Throw them inside!
You think you can get away with this, huh?
Leave me!
Trader!
You won't be able to
get away with this, trader!
Unroll it!
You will pay for all this!
Fatma!
Fatma Hatun!
Osman.
Your heart is in my hands, Osman.
Veronica!
You won't be able to get away with this!
Take her.
Fatma Hatun!
Throw her inside!
Get ready!
We are going to Akhisar!
I have a gift for them
Fatma Hatun.
Fatma Hatun, wake up!
Wake up!
Merchant!
This will be your end!
You will pay for this!
I swear you will pay for this!
Like we spoke, when the siege starts...
...Bayhan and Gencer Beys
will protect the army’s flanks.
As you command my Bey!
Osman Bey.
Ilbay, did you find any trace?
I did, my Bey.
The one that martyred
Baysungur and our spies...
...is a guest of Commander Lucas.
I don’t know her name.
No one knows her name in the
castle. All I know that it's a woman.
A woman with Lucas.
A hatun with devil eyes.
She is working together
with Lucas and Karesi Bey.
I know Karesi. Tell me about the others.
My Bey.
Lucas is waiting for you
at Akhisar with his armies.
That's all I know.
I couldn't learn anything else.
But you could expect
anything from that woman.
Okay.
You can go back.
They are planning something in Akhisar?
Beys, alps. The preparations are complete.
We will ruin their plans.
Akhisar will become Turks' land today.
God willing, my Bey.
But that demon woman.
We have a score to settle.
And I will take her life.
Come on.
We were attacked, Bala Hatun!
We were attacked!
Yusuf's alp!
Hold him!
What happened?
Tell me what happened.
They kidnapped Fatma Hatun.
Fatma?
What was Fatma doing there?
We were attacked on the road.
What about Yusuf?
Saruca?
They were taken prisoner.
Oh Allah! Saruca!
Oh Allah, take my life instead!
Allah!
Bring the horses
Take him to the healing tent!
What are we going to do?
Oh Allah, protect my child.
Bring my horse!
Come on!
I told you I’d cut out
your lifeline Osman.
Fatma Hatun.
Are you okay Fatma Hatun?
Saruca Bey?
Yusuf Bey? You..
Why are you here?
You...You..
Merchant Veronika!
You...You snake!
I'm not Veronika.
I am your father's and
the Turk's biggest enemy.
What do you want to do?
Tell me where we're going!
If you're brave release these
chains and face me! Come on!
Bravery?
I am the apocalypse.
I'll end Osman and Bala..
But first...
...I'll give them pain before they die.
I'm not afraid of you
You'll never get away with this!
Never!
Don't you ever think of consequences?
You'll pay for this merchant.
You'll pay greatly.
Shut up!
You're my slaves from now on.
I'm not afraid of you!
I'm not afraid of you! I'll never be!
Let us go! Let us go!
What you're doing won't
go unpunished! Never!
Of course.
Of course Fatma Hatun. Don't be afraid.
Fatma Hatun
These dastards can’t hurt you.
I'll protect you.
I'll protect you with
my own life if I have to.
I'll get you to your tribe safely.
Me too Fatma Hatun. Me too.
I'll die..
...before I let them take you.
If you want to die so much..
...just wait.
I'll take you to the grave.
Gladly.
Fatma!
Mother. Where’s Fatma?
What did they do to you?
They kidnapped Fatma Hatun.
We couldn't stop them.
Who did it?
We don't know Bala Hatun.
They took Saruca Bey and Yusuf Bey too.
Yusuf?
Brother?
Indeed, we belong to Allah,
and indeed, to Him we return.
What did they do to our children?
Is he alive Gonca Hatun?
He is. But he fainted.
Saruca.
This is Saruca's.
My son.
Dastards!
What did you do to our children?
My son!
Dastards!
Alps!
Send word to Alps and watchers!
Search everywhere.
The castles nearby...
...and the tribes.
Don't wait here.
Mother.
Who took Fatma?
Where are they going?
We'll find all 3 of them Gonca!
We will.
They went that way.
You stay here and tend to the wounded.
I'll go after them.
Okay mother.
Come on
Bala Hatun.
I'll come with you.
Come on.
How could they do this?
How could you?
Come on sisters.
Commander Lucas.
Osman Bey is coming up
to the walls with his army.
Osman.
I'm glad Karesi Bey couldn't stop you.
Since Sofia didn't send word..
...it's my pleasure to kill you.
Come on Hristo.
Let's welcome Osman.
You devil..
Let's see...
...if you're as brave as you say you are.
Osman Bey.
Welcome.
But you'll wish you never came here today.
If there is someone who is
going to wish for something...
...then it will be you Lucas.
When my sword is up on your neck...
...you'll be wishing for my mercy.
Now.
Either you give the castle to me...
Or?
Or you'll die with all those infidels.
Won't you see the
waIls I'm standing on?
Besides..
I have more men in this castle...
...than your army.
We climbed so many walls like these.
Karadin is the biggest proof of that.
But if you're talking about
the amount of men we have...
...you’re wrong once again, Lucas.
One of my men is
worth five of your knights.
But if you say don't let my
knights die, let's not battle...
...then come face me.
Here is the battlefield, here you are...
..and here I stand.
Come let us fight.
Fight...
You're asking me to duel you, is that it?
Let's see...
...if you have the bravery
and strength to face me.
You did a good thing for
your army, commander.
But I can't say
the same for you.
Get them out.
Bring them to me.
Stay close to me.
Break them.
Damn you.
Run away and save yourself.
She wants you, not us.
Yusuf is right.
Go now.
No, we're going to
leave together. Come on!
Idiots!
Where are you running?
This is my world.
You can't get out of here without dying!
We are never afraid of death, dastard!
-Come on!
-This way! Come on!
My soldiers.
Both will die with a single mistake.
Fatma
If you don’t behave..
I'll take your life.
You will pay for this, you ignoble!
-You think so?
-I do.
-No! No!
-Tie their hands!
-Brother!
-Take them!
Why did you accept this duel, Osman Bey?
We've surrounded the castle!
We could capture it, for sure!
If he hadn’t accepted my offer...
...then, we would have
washed these walls with blood.
Thank Allah, we have
the opportunity to take...
...this castle without
giving one single martyr.
Orhan.
My Bey.
If I fall as a martyr here...
...you will return with the army.
As you Command, my Bey.
Osman is a cunning warrior,
Commander. Be careful.
He's not cunning as much as I am.
Orhan.
Come here.
In the name of Allah, the
merciful, the beneficent.
Since you've come to these
lands, the devil is everywhere.
It's enough. It's time
for you to pay the price.
You will pay the price with your life.
Let's see then.
Come on, my Bey.
Ignoble! He's cheating.
Stop there, Alaaddin
You don't care to cheat even before
the warriors in the battleground, huh?
Why did we stop?
Trails end here.
But there's only Akhisar
castle on this side of the forest.
Come. on. To Akhisar castle.
Come on.
Let me go. Let go!
Akhisar will be the end of
you and your father Fatma.
My father will save us.
He won’t let us stay in
the nest of devils! Let go!
Walk!
Akhisar, Karadin or the other
lands you took from Byzantine...
None of them will be
yours Osman. None of them.
All of the people that you share blood
with who faced me ended up in hell.
You will share the same end.
Praise be!
Lucas huh? Lucas..
No Osman, no.
I won’t die today.
I won't by your hands.
-No!
-You say so?
My Bey!
Osman Bey!
Osman! Fatma!
What happened to Fatma?
Osman!
Your daughter, Fatma, is here.
Fatma!
Sister!
My Fatma
You ignoble dogs!
You faceless dog! You, dastard!
If you touch my
daughter, if your hurt her...
...you'll find yourself in the grave.
You, too, Lukas! You, too!
I'll erase both of you from this world!